I can't believe she did something so ridiculous.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنها فعلت شيئًا سخيفًا كهذا.
I'm going to talk to her father right now.
سأتحدث مع والدها الآن.
Actually, forget it.
في الواقع، انسى الأمر.
I don't believe you dare to offend Commander Xu.
لا أعتقد أنك تجرؤ على الإساءة إلى القائد شو.
Yiyu.
ممكن.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
When I take control of the Liu family in the future,
عندما أتولى السيطرة على عائلة ليو في المستقبل،
I'll definitely get justice for you.
بالتأكيد سأحصل على العدالة لك.
Do you like the birthday gift I got for you?
هل أعجبتك هدية عيد الميلاد التي أحضرتها لك؟
I found the best tailor in the city
لقد وجدت أفضل خياط في المدينة
to custom-make this with the finest fabric.
لصنع هذا خصيصًا باستخدام أجود أنواع الأقمشة.
I think
أظن
you'll look beautiful in it.
سوف تبدو جميلة فيه.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
Please don't come to see me unless necessary.
من فضلك لا تأتي لرؤيتي إلا إذا كان ذلك ضروريا.
After all, I'm married to your elder brother now.
بعد كل شيء، أنا متزوجة من أخيك الأكبر الآن.
You should address me as sister-in-law.
ينبغي عليك أن تناديني بـ "أخت الزوج".
Yiyu, are you alright?
يييو، هل أنت بخير؟
My wife doesn't need your concern, brother-in-law.
زوجتي لا تحتاج إلى قلقك يا أخي الزوج.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Open it and see.
افتحه وانظر.
Isn't it your birthday today?
أليس اليوم عيد ميلادك؟
Don't look anymore.
لا تنظر بعد الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I'm glad you like it.
أنا سعيد لأنك تحبه.
You're still not well.
أنت لست على ما يرام بعد.
Rest a bit more.
إرتاحي قليلا.
Liu Silin.
ليو سيلين.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I want you to help me with something.
أريدك أن تساعدني في شيء ما.
The truth about the Fulu Restaurant case from 10 years ago.
الحقيقة حول قضية مطعم الفولو قبل 10 سنوات.
Extra! Extra!
إضافي! إضافي!
The case at Fulu Restaurant from ten years ago!
قضية مطعم فولو قبل عشر سنوات!
By the looks of it.
من مظهره.
The master won't make it through this winter.
لن يتمكن السيد من تجاوز هذا الشتاء.
Don't talk nonsense. Don't let the master hear you.
لا تتكلم هراءً. لا تدع سيدك يسمعك.
But the Second Young Master has been managing the business so well lately.
لكن الشاب الثاني تمكن من إدارة الأعمال بشكل جيد في الآونة الأخيرة.
The master has nothing to worry about anymore.
لم يعد لدى السيد ما يدعو للقلق بعد الآن.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Everyone can see the Second Young Master's abilities.
الجميع يستطيع رؤية قدرات الشاب الثاني.
These are this month's accounts for the bank, dock, and medicine shop businesses.
هذه هي حسابات هذا الشهر للبنك والميناء ومتاجر الأدوية.
Please review them.
يرجى مراجعتها.
No need to look.
لا حاجة للنظر.
You can handle it all.
يمكنك التعامل مع كل ذلك.
Don't worry, Father.
لا تقلق يا أبي.
Yes.
نعم.
The master truly has a son worthy of his father.
إن السيد لديه حقًا ابنًا يستحق والده.
The Liu family has a worthy successor indeed.
إن عائلة ليو لديها خليفة جدير بالفعل.
Yes. Since the Second Young Master took over the business,
نعم. منذ أن تولى السيد الشاب الثاني إدارة العمل،
all the Liu family businesses have improved.
لقد تحسنت جميع أعمال عائلة ليو.
Profits are increasing daily,
الأرباح تتزايد يوميا،
and we all have better prospects now.
والآن أصبح لدينا جميعا آفاق أفضل.
Sinan,
سنان،
I have one more thing to tell you.
عندي شيء آخر أريد أن أخبرك به.
Father, please speak.
أبي من فضلك تكلم.
I'm listening.
انا أستمع.
Our Liu family
عائلتنا ليو
has been running legitimate businesses for generations.
لقد كان يدير أعمالًا مشروعة منذ أجيال.
You understand certain principles.
أنت تفهم مبادئ معينة.
No matter how much money we could make,
بغض النظر عن مقدار المال الذي يمكننا كسبه،
illegal activities
الأنشطة غير القانونية
are absolutely off-limits.
هي محظورة تماما.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
Father, rest assured.
أبي، اطمئن.
I will follow your teachings.
سأتبع تعاليمك.
Good.
جيد.
How is the Fulu Restaurant doing lately?
كيف حال مطعم فولو في الآونة الأخيرة؟
Since Chef Jiang Huai's incident,
منذ حادثة الشيف جيانغ هواي،
no one has been able to make the restaurant's signature dishes.
لم يتمكن أحد من صنع الأطباق المميزة للمطعم.
The revenue has been mediocre for years.
لقد كانت الإيرادات متوسطة لسنوات.
And lately, there's been no improvement.
ومؤخرا لم يكن هناك أي تحسن.
The First Young Master has mental illness after all.
السيد الشاب الأول يعاني من مرض عقلي بعد كل شيء.
His health is poor.
صحته سيئة.
It's unrealistic to expect him to run the restaurant well.
من غير الواقعي أن نتوقع منه أن يدير المطعم بشكل جيد.
As long as he has something to do
طالما أن لديه شيئا ليفعله
and doesn't cause trouble,
ولا يسبب مشاكل،
that would be best.
هذا سيكون الأفضل.
Silin was such a bright child from a young age.
كان سيلين طفلاً ذكيًا منذ صغره.
I had hoped he would bring honor to our family
كنت آمل أن يجلب الشرف لعائلتنا
and make the Liu family even more prosperous.
وجعل عائلة ليو أكثر ازدهارًا.
I failed to guide him properly.
لقد فشلت في توجيهه بشكل صحيح.
Now,
الآن،
that he's willing to settle down,
أنه على استعداد للاستقرار،
I am truly relieved.
أنا مرتاحة حقا.
I hope he stays on the right path from now on.
أتمنى أن يبقى على الطريق الصحيح من الآن فصاعدا.
His mother,
والدته
her spirit in heaven must be comforted too.
ويجب أن تتعزى روحها التي في السماء أيضًا.
Though this restaurant is small,
على الرغم من أن هذا المطعم صغير،
it's still part of the Liu family's assets.
لا يزال جزءًا من أصول عائلة ليو.
If he can manage it well,
إذا كان بإمكانه إدارة الأمر بشكل جيد،
perhaps he'll achieve greater things in the future.
ربما سيحقق أشياء أعظم في المستقبل.
Sinan.
سنان.
You wouldn't have to work so hard.
لن تحتاج إلى العمل بجد.
Yes, Father.
نعم يا أبي.
Yiyu.
ممكن.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Are you feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
Almost recovered.
لقد تعافى تقريبا.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I'm here to report to my father about the business over the past two months.
أنا هنا لأخبر والدي عن الأعمال خلال الشهرين الماضيين.
What about you? Why are you here so late?
ماذا عنك؟ لماذا أنت هنا متأخرًا جدًا؟
I also have important matters to report to the master.
لدي أيضًا أمور مهمة أريد أن أبلغها إلى السيد.
What matters?
ما الذي يهم؟
You'll find out soon enough.
سوف تكتشف ذلك قريبا بما فيه الكفاية.
Watch out!
احذر!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Take off your mask.
اخلع قناعك
Silin.
يمسح.
Doctor, how is he?
دكتور كيف حاله؟
Don't worry, madam.
لا تقلقي سيدتي.
The knife didn't hit any vital organs.
لم تصب السكين أي عضو حيوي.
The young master is not in immediate danger.
السيد الشاب ليس في خطر مباشر.
He just needs rest due to blood loss.
يحتاج فقط إلى الراحة بسبب فقدان الدم.
Alright. I understand. Thank you.
حسناً، فهمت. شكراً لك.
Why are you so foolish?
لماذا أنت غبي هكذا؟
Why did you take the knife for me?
لماذا أخذت السكين من أجلي؟
I shouldn't have let you help me.
لا ينبغي لي أن أسمح لك بمساعدتي.
Liu Silin.
ليو سيلين.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I need your help with something.
أحتاج إلى مساعدتك في شيء ما.
I want you to spread a false rumor.
أريدك أن تنشر إشاعة كاذبة.
This way,
من هنا،
I can find my parents' real murderer.
أستطيع العثور على القاتل الحقيقي لوالديّ.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't die so easily.
لن أموت بسهولة.
You're awake. Have some water.
أنت مستيقظ. اشرب بعض الماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I've let you down.
لقد خذلتك.
Thank you for taking care of me all this time.
شكرا لك على رعايتك لي طوال هذا الوقت.
If you don't want me to take care of you,
إذا كنت لا تريد مني أن أعتني بك،
then stop getting yourself hurt.
إذن توقف عن إيذاء نفسك.
Did they catch the culprit?
هل تم القبض على الجاني؟
The servants chased him outside the mansion,
طارده الخدم خارج القصر،
but he still got away.
ولكنه لا يزال يبتعد.
I thought we could finally find who really killed your parents.
اعتقدت أننا قد نتمكن أخيرًا من العثور على من قتل والديك حقًا.
Let's not think about this now.
لا نفكر في هذا الآن.
We'll talk about it later.
سنتحدث عن ذلك لاحقًا.
If I had really died,
لو مت حقا،
would you have been sad?
هل كنت ستحزن؟
What nonsense are you talking?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Of course I would be sad.
بالطبع سوف اكون حزينا.
But I won't allow you to die by someone else's hand.
ولكنني لن أسمح لك بالموت على يد شخص آخر.
You can leave these tasks to the servants from now on.
بإمكانك ترك هذه المهام للخدم من الآن فصاعدا.
That assassin can easily enter the Liu residence.
يمكن لهذا القاتل الدخول بسهولة إلى مسكن ليو.
I'm afraid that...
أخشى أن...
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
No, it doesn't.
لا، لا يحدث ذلك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Promise me.
وعدني.
No matter who it's for in the future,
بغض النظر عمن هو في المستقبل،
don't hurt yourself again.
لا تؤذي نفسك مرة أخرى.
Young master! Something terrible has happened!
يا سيدي الشاب! لقد حدث شيء فظيع!
What is it? Why are you so flustered?
ما الأمر؟ لماذا أنت مرتبك هكذا؟
The master! The master is dying!
السيد! السيد يموت!
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Father, you can't abandon your son!
أبي لا يمكنك أن تتخلى عن ابنك!
Father, wake up! Look at me!
يا أبي، استيقظ! انظر إليّ!
It's me, Sinan, Father.
أنا سنان يا أبي.
Young master.
سيد شاب.
He was fine yesterday.
لقد كان بخير بالأمس.
How did this happen so suddenly?
كيف حدث هذا فجأة؟
I... I don't know.
انا...لا اعرف.
What kind of doctor are you?
ما نوع الطبيب الذي أنت عليه؟
I swear I'll shoot you dead.
أقسم أنني سأقتلك بالرصاص.
Young master, even if you kill me,
سيدي الشاب، حتى لو قتلتني،
I'm afraid your father is beyond saving.
أخشى أن والدك لا يمكن إنقاذه.
Young master, please don't do anything rash!
سيدي الشاب، من فضلك لا تفعل أي شيء متهور!
Get out!
اخرج!
All of you, get out!
جميعكم، اخرجوا!
Yu.
يو.
[Credits]
[الاعتمادات]